affiliatepotentials.com 2013-05-08

# Wolo Marketing Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy Statement 

We are committed to keeping all your personal details safe and secure. Our privacy policy strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Collecting Your Personal Information

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). We will not pass on your details to any third party and do not send out marketing e-mails to customers unless they have registered to receive such material, purchased from us, or downloaded one of our free or paid products.

The type of information we ‘may’ collect about you includes:

Your full name  
Your e-mail address  
Your postal address

IP information 

Generally, this information is requested when you are either downloading free products, when you purchase any of our products (eBooks, software etc.), or when you subscribe to our newsletters. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by e-mailing us at: support@wolomarketing.com. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

By signing up for wolomarketing.com products/offers you agree to have mail sent to you from Nick, Peter, Yvonne or wolomarketing.com. See "How we use your personal information" for further information.

**How We Control Your Personal Information**

We will not use your personal information for any other reason other than to contact you. We do not sell, give away or rent your email address to any third party. If in the future we did for any reason wish to rent, sell or use your email address for any other purpose we will ask you for your permission first.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

Your personal information is used for four main purposes and they are as follows:

1\. To send out information, recommendations and resources to you.

2\. To provide assistance to you after you have purchased products from us.

3\. To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.

4\. To enlighten you about new products, services, tool, upgrades, special offers and information which I feel may be of use to you. 

We will only disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

(a) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on www.wolomarketing.com;

(b) Protect and defend the rights or property of www.wolomarketing.com;

(c) Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of www.wolomarketing.com.
